Dot Net Developer

Name: Mohamed Gaber Sobhy Afify

Address: El Zahraa /Nasr City /Cairo/Egypt

Email: Eng.bahrawy89@Gmail.com

Mobile No: (+2)01206570373

Dear HR Manager:

This letter is to express my interest for an experienced Software Developer. With a Bachelor's degree in **Computer Science**, and hands-on experience using **.Net tools** to create and implement software applications, I am confident I will be an asset to your organization.

I enjoy being challenged and engaging with projects that require me to work outside my comfort and knowledge set, as continuing to learn **new languages** and development techniques are important to me and the success of your organization.

Your listed requirements closely match my background and skills. A few I would like to highlight that would enable me to contribute to your bottom line are:

Educations:

- Graduated from Faculty of Computer and Information Systems Helwan University (2012).
- Department of information systems.
- Graduation project was **Online Website** for El-Rahma Hospital Using .**Net Technology.**

Studied Courses:

- Database Management System Analysis
- Data Communication
- Data Mining
- Data warehouse
- System analysis

- C&C++ Programming Language
- Java Programming Language
- Network
- Artificial Intelligence
- Operating Systems

Qualifications:

- MVC4 (C#)
- WPF (C#)
- Windows Form (C#)
- Windows Form (VB6)
- MSQL
- HtmlAgilityBack

- SQL Entity Framework
- JavaScript(JQuery)
- Html5
- CSS3
- Crystal Report 8.5
- ItextSharp

Experience:

United Arabs company:

Software & Hardware Maintenance (From 7/2012 to 12/2012)

Page 1 of 2

• Kirby Egypt:

IT Specialist(From 6/2014 to 7/2015)

• All Localized:

IT Specialist & Graphic Design (From 8/2015 to 10/2016)

• OrascomConstruction(Al-Borolos Power Station):

Software Developer(from 11/2016 to 10/2017)

• Medical Union Pharmaceuticals(MUP):

Software Developer (from 11/2017 till now)

Projects:

In OrascomConstruction(Al-Borolos Power Station):

Project Name	Description	Tools
PDF Navigator	Windows Application to Search/Find Specific word(s) in Multiple PDF Files. It	WPF,C#, itextsharp and
(Individual)	Returns File Name and Page number and Paragraph Contains the text	MSSQL
Cars Movement	Windows Application, Recording Company's Cars movement	Windows Form, C#,.Net,
(Individual)	(Transport/Maintenance). Output: Cars expenses in a specific period , Cars	Crystal report and MSSQL
	traveled distance(KM), Drivers list , Car drivers, Driver Cars , Available Cars	
	And Not Available Cars Report	
Employee INQ	Web based application that enables users to connect each other in Orascom	MVC4, JavaScript, Ajax,
(Individual)	electrical power plant, It display the employee contact details, work location,	Css3, Html5 and MSSQL
	employee/engineer managed sectors and employees under leadership.	

• In Medical Union Pharmaceuticals(MUP):

Project Name	Description	Tools
General Accounts	Following up company income and outcome (check/cash), It Displays:	Windows Form, C#,.Net,
	Customer/company credit & debt , net Profit and check due dates	Crystal report and MSSQL
Company Assets	Divide short age Assets to specific period of time(5yrs) to calculate the	Windows Form, C#,.Net,
	Depreciation	Crystal report and MSSQL
PDf Parser	Extracting all data in text format into tables format (Item, value) for statistics	WPF,C#, ItextSharp,
	process	HtmlAgilityBack and MSSQL

Skills:

- Adobe Photoshop
- Adobe Illustrator
- Adobe InDesign
- Adobe FrameWork
- MS Office

Personal Skills:

- Self-learner
- Quick learner
- Fast Adaptive
- Hard worker
- Good Communication Skills